The Gilbert and Lila Silverman Fluxus Collection Archives
The Museum of Modern Art, Publisher
- Series VII: Silverman Administrative Files, 1974-2010
  - Subseries VII.B: Exhibition Loans
    - Japanese Art After 1945. Guggenheim Museum, New York. September 14, 1994 - January 8, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 264, Folder VII.B.291)
    - Japanese Art After 1945. Guggenheim Museum, New York. September 14, 1994 - January 8, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 264, Folder VII.B.292)
    - Neo-Dada. Scottsdale Center for the Arts. November 4, 1994 - January 1, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 264, Folder VII.B.293)
    - Duchamp's Leg. Walker Art Center, Minneapolis. November 5, 1994 - March 26, 1995., 1994-1996; Loan documentation. (Box 264, Folder VII.B.294)
    - Duchamp's Leg. Walker Art Center, Minneapolis. November 5, 1994 - March 26, 1995., 1994-1995; Ephemera; loan documentation. (Box 264, Folder VII.B.295)
    - Duchamp's Leg. Walker Art Center, Minneapolis. November 5, 1994 - March 26, 1995., 1994-1996; Loan documentation. (Box 264, Folder VII.B.296)
    - Dick Higgins. Henie-Onstad Kunstsenter, Høvikodden. January 1995 - May 1996., 1993-1996; Loan documentation. (Box 264, Folder VII.B.297)
    - Dick Higgins. Henie-Onstad Kunstsenter, Høvikodden. January 1995 - May 1996., 1994-1997; Loan documentation. (Box 264, Folder VII.B.298)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., undated; Photographs of works lent. (Box 265, Folder VII.B.299)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., undated; Loan documentation (photocopies of Fluxus 1 lent). (Box 265, Folder VII.B.300)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., Loan documentation; ephemera. (Box 265, Folder VII.B.301)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., Loan documentation; exhibition planning; related correspondence. (Box 265, Folder VII.B.302)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 265, Folder VII.B.303)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 265, Folder VII.B.304)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 265, Folder VII.B.305)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 265, Folder VII.B.306)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 265, Folder VII.B.307)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 265, Folder VII.B.308)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 265, Folder VII.B.309)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 265, Folder VII.B.310)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 265, Folder VII.B.311)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 265, Folder VII.B.312)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., 1994-1995; Loan documentation. (Box 266, Folder VII.B.313)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., Catalogue preparations; draft of Hendricks essay. (Box 266, Folder VII.B.314)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., Catalogue preparations; draft of Hendricks essay. (Box 266, Folder VII.B.315)
    - L'art du Tampon. Muse de la Poste, Paris. May 4 - August 26, 1995., 1995-1996; Loan documentation. (Box 266, Folder VII.B.316)
    - Eine lange Geschichte mit vielen Knoten: Fluxus in Deutschland 1962-1994. Institut fr Auslandsbeziehungen, Stuttgart. May 14 - June 25, 1995., Loan documentation; ephemera; press. (Box 266, Folder VII.B.317)
    - Japanese Art After 1945. San Francisco Museum of Modern Art. May 31 - August 27, 1995., Loan documentation; press. (Box 266, Folder VII.B.318)
    - Japanese Art After 1945. San Francisco Museum of Modern Art. May 31 - August 27, 1995., Loan documentation. (Box 266, Folder VII.B.319)
    - Japanese Art After 1945. San Francisco Museum of Modern Art. May 31 - August 27, 1995., Itineraries. (Box 266, Folder VII.B.320)
    - Revolution: Art of the Sixties from Warhol to Beuys. Museum of Contemporary Art, Tokyo. September 30 - December 10, 1995., Ephemera; loan documentation. (Box 267, Folder VII.B.321)
    - Revolution: Art of the Sixties from Warhol to Beuys. Museum of Contemporary Art, Tokyo. September 30 - December 10, 1995., Ephemera; loan documentation. (Box 267, Folder VII.B.322)
    - Revolution: Art of the Sixties from Warhol to Beuys. Museum of Contemporary Art, Tokyo. September 30 - December 10, 1995., Loan documentation. (Box 267, Folder VII.B.323)
    - Revolution: Art of the Sixties from Warhol to Beuys. Museum of Contemporary Art, Tokyo. September 30 - December 10, 1995., Exhibition planning. (Box 267, Folder VII.B.324)
    - Revolution: Art of the Sixties from Warhol to Beuys. Museum of Contemporary Art, Tokyo. September 30 - December 10, 1995., Exhibition planning. (Box 267, Folder VII.B.325)
    - Revolution: Art of the Sixties from Warhol to Beuys. Museum of Contemporary Art, Tokyo. September 30 - December 10, 1995., Exhibition planning; loan documentation. (Box 267, Folder VII.B.326)
    - Revolution: Art of the Sixties from Warhol to Beuys. Museum of Contemporary Art, Tokyo. September 30 - December 10, 1995., Exhibition planning. (Box 267, Folder VII.B.327)
    - Revolution: Art of the Sixties from Warhol to Beuys. Museum of Contemporary Art, Tokyo. September 30 - December 10, 1995., Loan documentation. (Box 267, Folder VII.B.328)
    - Revolution: Art of the Sixties from Warhol to Beuys. Museum of Contemporary Art, Tokyo. September 30 - December 10, 1995., undated; Exhibition planning. (Box 267, Folder VII.B.329)
    - Revolution: Art of the Sixties from Warhol to Beuys. Museum of Contemporary Art, Tokyo. September 30 - December 10, 1995., undated; Exhibition planning. (Box 267, Folder VII.B.330)
    - Revolution: Art of the Sixties from Warhol to Beuys. Museum of Contemporary Art, Tokyo. September 30 - December 10, 1995., Notes and text for Hendricks lecture. (Box 267, Folder VII.B.331)
    - Revolution: Art of the Sixties from Warhol to Beuys. Museum of Contemporary Art, Tokyo. September 30 - December 10, 1995., Ephemera; exhibition planning; condition reports. (Box 267, Folder VII.B.332)
    - In the Spirit of Fluxus. Hessenhuis, Antwerp. October 21, 1995 - January 28, 1996., Ephemera; press; exhibition planning. (Box 268, Folder VII.B.333)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Art - Amusement. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. January 23 - February 25, 1996., 1995-1996; Exhibition planning; ephemera. (Box 268, Folder VII.B.334)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Art - Amusement. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. January 23 - February 25, 1996., 1995-1996; Exhibition planning; ephemera; press; loan documentation. (Box 268, Folder VII.B.335)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Art - Amusement. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. January 23 - February 25, 1996., 1995-1996; Exhibition planning; loan documentation. (Box 268, Folder VII.B.336)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Art - Amusement. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. January 23 - February 25, 1996., 1995; Draft of Hendricks essay for catalogue. (Box 268, Folder VII.B.337)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Art - Amusement. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. January 23 - February 25, 1996., 1995-1996; Concerns Hendricks trip to Vilnius and Copenhagen. (Box 268, Folder VII.B.338)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Art - Amusement. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. January 23 - February 25, 1996., Ephemera; press. (Box 268, Folder VII.B.339)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Art - Amusement. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. January 23 - February 25, 1996., 1996-1998; Ephemera; exhibition planning; other correspondence, including with Vytautas Landsbergis. (Box 268, Folder VII.B.340)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Art - Amusement. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. January 23 - February 25, 1996., 1994-1998; Ephemera; exhibition planning; other correspondence. (Box 268, Folder VII.B.341)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Art - Amusement. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. January 23 - February 25, 1996., Loan documentation. (Box 268, Folder VII.B.342)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Art - Amusement. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. January 23 - February 25, 1996., 1994-1995; Loan documentation; exhibition planning. (Box 268, Folder VII.B.343)
    - Fluxus Art Amusement. Randers Kunstmuseum. May 2-28, 1996., Exhibition planning; ephemera. (Box 268, Folder VII.B.344)
    - Fluxus Art Amusement. Randers Kunstmuseum. May 2-28, 1996., Exhibition planning; ephemera; loan documentation. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.345)
    - Fluxus Art Amusement. Randers Kunstmuseum. May 2-28, 1996., Exhibition planning; press; loan documentation. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.346)
    - Fluxus Art Amusement. Randers Kunstmuseum. May 2-28, 1996., Installation photographs. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.347)
    - Fluxus Art Amusement. Randers Kunstmuseum. May 2-28, 1996., Installation photographs. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.348)
    - Shit. Baron/Boisant Editions, New York. September 17 - November 16, 1996., Loan documentation. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.349)
    - Fluxus Art Amusement. Stiftung Starke, Berlin. October 18 - November 16, 1996., Loan documentation; ephemera; exhibition planning. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.350)
    - Fluxus Art Amusement. Stiftung Starke, Berlin. October 18 - November 16, 1996., Loan documentation; ephemera; exhibition planning. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.351)
    - Yoko Ono and Fluxus. Royal Festival Hall, London. February 6 - March 23, 1997., 1996-1997; Ephemera; press; loan documentation. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.352)
    - Yoko Ono and Fluxus. Royal Festival Hall, London. February 6 - March 23, 1997., 1993-1998; Exhibition planning; loan documentation. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.353)
    - Yoko Ono and Fluxus. Royal Festival Hall, London. February 6 - March 23, 1997., Press. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.354)
    - Yoko Ono and Fluxus. Royal Festival Hall, London. February 6 - March 23, 1997., Installation photographs. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.355)
    - Yoko Ono and Fluxus. Royal Festival Hall, London. February 6 - March 23, 1997., Loan documentation. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.356)
    - The best of Wim T. Schippers. Centraal Museum, Utrecht. February 28 - May 4, 1997., 1996-1997; Loan documentation. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.357)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Cabinet. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. Beginning June 17, 1997., Photographs; press; related correspondence. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.358)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Cabinet. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. Beginning June 17, 1997., Exhibition planning; loan documentation. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.359)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Cabinet. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. Beginning June 17, 1997., Exhibition planning; loan documentation; checklists. (Box 269, Folder VII.B.360)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Cabinet. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. Beginning June 17, 1997., Ephemera. (Box 270, Folder VII.B.361)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Cabinet. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. Beginning June 17, 1997., Exhibition planning. (Box 270, Folder VII.B.362)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Cabinet. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. Beginning June 17, 1997., Concerns Hendricks trip to Vilnius. (Box 270, Folder VII.B.363)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Cabinet. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. Beginning June 17, 1997., Ephemera; installation photographs; exhibition correspondence. (Box 270, Folder VII.B.364)
    - George Maciunas: Fluxus Cabinet. The Contemporary Art Center of Vilnius. Beginning June 17, 1997., 2003; Concerns possible travel to France. (Box 270, Folder VII.B.365)
    - Sound Objects. Whitney Museum of American Art, New York. June 18 - September 7, 1997., Loan documentation. (Exhibition was cancelled.) (Box 270, Folder VII.B.366)
    - Yoko Ono. Museum of Modern Art, Oxford. November 23, 1997 - March 15, 1998., 1997-1998; Loan documentation. (Box 270, Folder VII.B.367)
    - Yoko Ono. Museum of Modern Art, Oxford. November 23, 1997 - March 15, 1998., 1997-1998; Loan documentation. (Box 270, Folder VII.B.368)
    - Artists Talk on Art film screening. December 5, 1997., Loan documentation. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.369)
    - Blink. Gracie Mansion Gallery, New York. January 20 - February 14, 1998., 1997-1998; Loan documentation. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.370)
    - Jukebox, permanent installation at Nicolaj, Copenhagen Contemporary Art Center. Beginning February 5, 1998., Loan documentation. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.371)
    - Out of Actions. Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles. February 8 - May 10, 1998., 1997-1998; Loan documentation. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.372)
    - Out of Actions. Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles. February 8 - May 10, 1998., 1997-1998; Loan documentation. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.373)
    - Deep Storage. Multiple Venues. June 1998 - January 1999., 1998-1999; Ephemera; loan documentation, including concerning exhibition's travel to Munich, Berlin, Dsseldorf, New York, and Seattle. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.374)
    - Transmit. Queens Borough Public Library. February 3 - March 28, 1999., 1998-1999; Loan documentation; ephemera. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.375)
    - Transmit. Queens Borough Public Library. February 3 - March 28, 1999., Ephemera. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.376)
    - Off Limits: Rutgers University and the Avant Garde. Newark Museum. February 18 - May 16, 1999., 1998-1999; Loan documentation. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.377)
    - Off Limits: Rutgers University and the Avant Garde. Newark Museum. February 18 - May 16, 1999., 1998-1999; Loan documentation. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.378)
    - Off Limits: Rutgers University and the Avant Garde. Newark Museum. February 18 - May 16, 1999., 1998-1999; Loan documentation. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.379)
    - Off Limits: Rutgers University and the Avant Garde. Newark Museum. February 18 - May 16, 1999., 1998-1999; Loan documentation. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.380)
    - Robert Watts. Museum Fridericianum, Kassel. April 24 - July 18, 1999., Loan documentation. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.381)
    - Robert Watts. Museum Fridericianum, Kassel. April 24 - July 18, 1999., Regards conservation of damaged work by Robert Watts. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.382)
    - Robert Watts. Museum Fridericianum, Kassel. April 24 - July 18, 1999., Regards conservation of damaged work by Robert Watts. (Box 271, Folder VII.B.383)
    - Robert Watts. Museum Fridericianum, Kassel. April 24 - July 18, 1999., Ephemera. (Box 272, Folder VII.B.384)
    - Robert Watts. Museum Fridericianum, Kassel. April 24 - July 18, 1999., Regards conservation of damaged work by Robert Watts. (Box 272, Folder VII.B.385)
    - Global Conceptualism. Queens Museum of Art, New York. April 28 - August 29, 1999., Loan documentation. (Box 272, Folder VII.B.386)
    - World Views: Maps and Art. Frederick R. Weisman Museum, University of Minnesota. September 11, 1999 - January 31, 2000., 1999-2000; Loan documentation; ephemera. (Box 272, Folder VII.B.387)
    - The American Century. Whitney Musuem of American Art, New York. September 26, 1999 - February 13, 2000., 1999-2000; Loan documentation; ephemera. (Box 272, Folder VII.B.388)
    - Food / Gordon Matta Clark. Landesmuseum fr Kunst und Kulturgeschichte, Mnster. October 3, 1999 - January 2, 2000., 1999-2004; Loan documentation; ephemera. (Box 272, Folder VII.B.389)
    - Experiments in the Everyday: Allan Kaprow and Robert Watts. Wallach Art Gallery, Columbia University. October 5 - December 4, 1999., 1998-2000; Loan documentation; press. (Box 272, Folder VII.B.390)
    - Art-Worlds in Dialogue. Museum Ludwig, Cologne. October 7, 1999 - April 19, 2000., 1999-2000; Loan documentation. (Box 272, Folder VII.B.391)
    - The Worlds of Nam June Paik. Guggenheim Museum, New York. February 11 - April 26, 2000., 1999-2000; Loan documentation. (Box 272, Folder VII.B.392)
    - The Worlds of Nam June Paik. Guggenheim Museum, New York. February 11 - April 26, 2000., 1999-2001; Loan documentation, including concerning exhibition's travel to Seoul and Bilbao. (Box 272, Folder VII.B.393)
    - The Worlds of Nam June Paik. Guggenheim Museum, New York. February 11 - April 26, 2000., 2000-2002; Loan documentation, including concerning exhibition's travel to Seoul and Bilbao. (Box 272, Folder VII.B.394)
    - The Worlds of Nam June Paik. Guggenheim Museum, New York. February 11 - April 26, 2000., Loan documentation, including copy photographs. (Box 272, Folder VII.B.395)
    - Time Suspend Your Flight. Bergen Kunstmuseum. March 25 - May 14, 2000., 1999-2000; Ephemera; loan documentation. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.396)
    - Experiments in the Everyday: Allan Kaprow and Robert Watts. List Visual Arts Center, Massachusetts Institute of Technology. April 27 - July 2, 2000., 1999-2000; Loan documentation. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.397)
    - Fluxus display. Tate Modern, London. Beginning May 11, 2000., 2000-2002; Loan documentation; press. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.398)
    - Fluxus display. Tate Modern, London. Beginning May 11, 2000., 2000-2002; Loan documentation. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.399)
    - Fluxus display. Tate Modern, London. Beginning May 11, 2000., 2000-2002; Loan documentation. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.400)
    - Fluxus display. Tate Modern, London. Beginning May 11, 2000., Photographs from opening. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.401)
    - Global Conceptualism. Miami Art Museum. June 23 - August 27, 2000., Invitation to opening. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.402)
    - Language and Utopia in 20th Century Art. Palais des Beaux-Arts, Brussels. June 23 - September 24, 2000. Museu d'Art Contemporani, Barcelona. October 19, 2000 - January 9, 2001., 1999; Loan request. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.403)
    - Time Suspend Your Flight. Reykjavk Art Museum. August 12 - October 10, 2000., 1999-2000; Loan documentation. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.404)
    - The New Frontier: Art and Television, 1960-1965. Austin Museum of Art. September 1 - November 26, 2000., Loan documentation. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.405)
    - The New Frontier: Art and Television, 1960-1965. Austin Museum of Art. September 1 - November 26, 2000., 2000-2001; Loan documentation; ephemera; press. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.406)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Invitations. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.407)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Loan documentation. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.408)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Loan documentation. (Box 273, Folder VII.B.409)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Press. (Box 274, Folder VII.B.410)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Exhibition planning. (Box 274, Folder VII.B.411)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Exhibition planning. (Box 274, Folder VII.B.412)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Loan documentation. (Box 274, Folder VII.B.413)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., undated; Source material for wall texts. (Box 274, Folder VII.B.414)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Loan documentation. (Box 274, Folder VII.B.415)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Checklist. (Box 274, Folder VII.B.416)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Loan documentation. (Box 274, Folder VII.B.417)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Exhibition planning. (Box 274, Folder VII.B.418)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Installation photographs. (Box 274, Folder VII.B.419)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Loan documentation. (Box 274, Folder VII.B.420)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Checklist. (Box 274, Folder VII.B.421)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Checklist. (Box 274, Folder VII.B.422)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Loan documentation. (Box 275, Folder VII.B.423)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Loan documentation. (Box 275, Folder VII.B.424)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., 2000-2001; Loan documentation; installation photographs. (Box 275, Folder VII.B.425)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., 2000-2001; Ephemera and other exhibition-related materials. (Box 275, Folder VII.B.426)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., 2000-2001; Press; loan documentation. (Box 275, Folder VII.B.427)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., 2000-2001; Loan documentation. (Box 275, Folder VII.B.428)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., 2000-2001; Installation photographs. (Box 275, Folder VII.B.429)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., 2000-2001; Exhibition planning. (Box 275, Folder VII.B.430)
    - What's Fluxus? What's Not! Why. Bergen Kunstmuseum. September 8, 2000 - August 15, 2001., Wall texts (from both Bergen and Brazil). (Box Flat File 2-5, Folder VII.B.431*)
    - YES Yoko Ono. Japan Society, New York. October 18, 2000 - January 14, 2001., Catalogue permissions; loan documentation. (Box 275, Folder VII.B.432)
    - Hard Pressed: 600 Years of Prints and Process. The Equitable Gallery, New York. (Organized by International Print Center, New York.) November 2, 2000 - January 14, 2001., 2000-2001; Loan documentation; ephemera. (Box 275, Folder VII.B.433)
    - Hard Pressed: 600 Years of Prints and Process. The Equitable Gallery, New York. (Organized by International Print Center, New York.) November 2, 2000 - January 14, 2001., 2000-2001; Loan documentation, including travel to other venues. (Box 275, Folder VII.B.434)
    - Hard Pressed: 600 Years of Prints and Process. The Equitable Gallery, New York. (Organized by International Print Center, New York.) November 2, 2000 - January 14, 2001., 2000-2001; Loan documentation, including travel to other venues. (Box 276, Folder VII.B.435)
    - Hard Pressed: 600 Years of Prints and Process. The Equitable Gallery, New York. (Organized by International Print Center, New York.) November 2, 2000 - January 14, 2001., 2000-2002; Loan documentation, including travel to other venues; condition reports. (Box 276, Folder VII.B.436)
    - Some Fluxus. Detroit Institute of Arts. February 23, 2001 - November 8, 2002., 2000-2001; Ephemera; loan documentation; wall texts. (Box 276, Folder VII.B.437)